

Vasilis Regginas

Frontend Web Developer

(1)

18 July 1996



Alexandrias 69 st. Daphne, Attika, Greece



+30 6955375331



http://en.wikipedia.org



vregginas@hotmail.com

About me —

I am Vasilis. I am 25 years old and I am a passionate coder. I love technology and it is a big part of my life just like most people, nowadays. I am a BA student of Sociology at Panteion university of Social and Political sciences in Athens. I am into web development since July 2021, learning things on my own and getting better everyday. In my free time, I like practising my coding skills and that is how I expand my progress. As a professional, I have a little freelance experience.



interests

Technology, Combat sports, Fitness

education

2016-PresentBA student in Sociology

Panteion University

2021-PresentSelf taught Frontend Web Developer

WorldWide Web

2011-2014 High school

Vasilikon, Evia Greece

experience

8/2016-8/2017Collection Agent

Mellon technologies

8/2017-3/2018Collection Agent

Charaktiniotis and partners law office

3/2018-1/2021 Collection Agent

Cepal

1/2021-7-2021 Private

Greek army

other information

I am an out-of-the-box thinker. Finding solutions and keeping calm under pressure is a huge part of my professional personality. I highly value teamwork and I always pursue it in my pro relationships, since it is a main factor to the achievement of goals. I am a fast-learner and always open to learning new things. I am seeking for a work environment that will give me the chance to grow and reach my goals.